ACTWU Legislative and Political Department Files 5619/033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU Legislative and Political Department Files
1947-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5619/033
38 cubic feet
38 linear ft.
Correspondence, records (documents).
6826768
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
K. Serraneau, March 02, 2011
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Biographical / Historical
The Legislative and Political Department was concerned with issues such as trade agreements, lobbying efforts, political party conventions and elections. When increased imports were supported by several United States presidential administrations the ACTWU decided that if the administration could not be persuaded to change trade policies that the union would lobby Congress to do so. The department helped mobilize and register voters, maintained a political action committee, distributed election information to members, and supported trade bills.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 AV: ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004 fiche: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Speeches on Microfiche 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/008: ACWA Rieve-Pollock Foundation Files 5619/009: ACTWU Operations Department Sidney Hillman Awards Files 5619/010: ACWA Jacob Potofsky files 5619/011: ACTWU Southern Regional Joint Board Files 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5619/013: ACTWU Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Legislative and Political Department; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6826768
- The American Footwear Act of 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Footwear Petition Signature House and Senate, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- TRADE--SHOES-- ITC Relief Case, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1984 ITC Correspondence Footwear (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Shoe Relief-1981, 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- TRADE-HEADWEAR- FRAUD- Korea and Taiwan, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Child Nutrition Act 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Children`s Issues 1977-1978, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Citizens for Tax Reform 1978- Early 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Coalition to Save New York, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Brown Lung 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cotton Dust Standard 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cooperative Bank 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Export -Import Bank- Long Amendment 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Hatch Act 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Hospital Cost Containment, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- H.R.3: Bill Text, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- TRADE- Tariff- Cutting Authority, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 1987 Book Nomination: Supreme Court (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  August
- Catastrophic Heath Care, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CETA program 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- H.R. 700- Civil Rights Restoration Act of 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Social Security Cuts, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Social Security Committee Minutes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  February 3
- Legal Services, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- American Shoe Industry Labor and Management Petition October 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  October 23
- Sri Lanka Amendment to H.R. 5339 Restrictions on certain A.I.D. funds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  May 30
- Darlington Case, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  May 27
- JEANS: FAA Regulations for Air- Traffic Controllers` Dress Code, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  July
- U.S. Policy in El Salvador, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- March for Jobs, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Hobbs Act 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Insurance: Women (non-discrimination), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  August 12
- Safety and Health/ OSHA New Directions Program, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Van de Water Nomination to NLRB, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  October 21
- IUD/ERIC Bill 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Government Procurement- Urban Areas, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Generic Trade Bill, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Israeli- U.S> Free Trade Agreement, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- TRADE- Israeli Free Trade Zone, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance- 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  July 31
- Trade Adjustment Assistance Amendment, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Gephardt Amendment, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  March 27
- TRADE H.R. 3 - Omnibus Trade Bill, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Energy- Windfall Profits Toy -1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  June 27
- H.R. 1616- Plant Closing Bill, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  August 28
- Plant Closing Legislation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Plant Closing Legislation 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Testimony- Plant Closings May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Plant Closing Legislation, 1970-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Subminimum Wage, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  March
- Minimum Wage- 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage- Max Hours- 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Minimum Wage Studies- 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage Legislation 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Minimum Wage, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Minimum Wage 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Political- 1984 Presidential Election ACTWU Member Poll, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Report- Poll, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1984 Presidential Campaign (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Voter Registration 1984- Computer Print -out Requests (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Voter Registration Mailings, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 1984 Presidential Campaign Brochure (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Presidential Campaign- Free Trade, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 1984 Presidential Election ACTWU Efforts (Box 4, Folder 5)
- North Carolina/ Helms Senate Race, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  March 24
- 1984 Senate Election, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  December 28
- 1984 Presidential Election-- Labor Procedure, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  August 27
- 1984 Presidential Election-- Status, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  May 20
- Mondale Campaign: New Hampshire, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Liz Speech Material, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Presidential Campaign: Telephone/ Office Leases, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  February 21
- Mondale Presidential Campaign- ACTWU Efforts, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Presidential Campaign: Assignment Letters, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  April 23
- Presidential Campaign: Communication Costs, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Regan Cabinet- Background, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Geraldine Ferraro, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 1984 Presidential Election- ACTWU- Delegate Possibilities (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 1984 House Races (Box 4, Folder 19)
  February
- Leadership Information, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  March 21
- 1984 Presidential Election- ACTWU General (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1984 Presidential Campaign, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  September 13
- 1984 Presidential Candidates Information, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  July 18
- 1984 Delegate Selection, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- DNC-- Women`s Caucus, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Correspondence with Members of Congress, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 1984 Election Information (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Campaign Projections
- 1984 Presidential Election Campaign- Mondale Campaign (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Presidential Nomination, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Democratic National Committee Proposals
- DNC-- Strategy Council, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  October 20
- 1984 DNC Platform (Box 4, Folder 31)
  September 11
- DNC-- Committees, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- DNC-- Finance Council, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Democratic National Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Democratic National Committee-- Officers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Presidential Nominating Process, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  March 17
- Democratic National Committee- Midterm Convention, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Democratic National Committee- Platform Accountability Commission, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Democratic National Committee-- Rules Committee, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  June 29
- Democratic National Committee-- Labor Commission, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Democratic National Committee-- Targeting Meetings, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  October 5
- Democratic National Committee-- Poll Report, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  January
- Democratic National Committee-- Resolutions Committee, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Jobs Training and Research Program, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- LIEBLER, Susan, Nomination to Court of Appeals, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- LCLAA-- Immigration Materials, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Immigration, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Immigration, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Hobbs Act, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance- 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Subsidies Code- 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  March 20
- New Tariff/ Trade Bills, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Trade Bill of 1984- 201 Reform, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- TRADE- Rules of Origin, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Economic Equity Act of 1987 (Pat Schroeder) ACTWU - endorsed (Box 5, Folder 8)
  July 7
- Multicultural Investment Guarantee Agency, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- M.F.A, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Trade Law Modernization Act and Omnibus Trade Act of 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- TRADE: Tariff- Cutting Authority, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  May 14
- H.R. 1950- Trade Law Modernization Act, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Anti- Counterfeiting Legislation 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Bill DuChessi, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Statement-- Jack Fair Practices in Auto products Act, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Statement-- Stanley Nehmer Leather Products Coalition, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Statement-- Jack Illegal and Unfair Foreign Trade Practices, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Citizens Against Nuclear War-- Nuclear Freeze, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Republican Platform-- Economic Reindustrialization, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  January 31
- Environment- General, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- TRADE- Industrial Policy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  November 10
- TRADE- General, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- TRADE- General, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- TRADE- Poland- Dumping Wool Suits, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- TRADE- Insular Possessions, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- TRADE- Non- Market Economy Legislation, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- HFA and Bilateral Negotiations, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- TRADE- Generalized System of Preferences, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- International trade Commission- Leather, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Senatorial Congressional Resolution 108- Leather, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Senatorial Congressional Resolution 108- Leather Wearing Apparel- Testimony, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Senatorial Congressional Resolution 107- Leather Wearing Apparel- Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Leather Wearing Apparel Industry- General Information, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Tariff Cutting Authority- H.R. 4761/ S.1902, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Tariff Cutting Authority- H.R. 4761/ S. 1902, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Tariff Cutting Authority- H.R. 4761, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- TRADE- Vredeling Proposal, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Statement on S. 1902, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- TRADE- Customs Service, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- TRADE- Section 807, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Labeling Act of 1939, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Labor Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- TRADE- Labor Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  July 14
- MFA Renewal, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- MFA Renewal, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- MFA Renewal, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Trade- Reorganization Plan 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- TRADE- 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- TRADE-General- 1979- Textile and Apparel (Box 6, Folder 23)
  July 13
- Non-rubber Footwear, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Leather Products Coalition, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  November 29
- Work Glove Manufacturers Association, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Luggage and Leather Goods Manufacturers of America, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- TRADE- Tariff Cutting Authority, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- TRADE- Informal Entry Legislation, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- TRADE: Wool Blend Tariff Legislation, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- TRADE: Generalized System of Preferences, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- TRADE: ATMI Legislative Subcommittee, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  November 15
- ST Representatives William Brock, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- TRADE: Cattle Hides Export Administration, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Comprehensive Trade Law Reform Act of 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- TRADE: 1983 Spring Offensive Import Resolution (Box 7, Folder 15)
- TRADE: Reciprocity (Tariff Cutting), 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- TRADE: Shoe Petition- 201 Escape Clause, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- TRADE: Shoe Imports, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- TRADE: Footwear Caucus, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- TRADE: 1982 Shoe Offensive (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Footwear Quota Bill, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Trade Negotiation, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Liz- 1982 Personal Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- 1980 Senate Campaign, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 1980 Presidential Campaign, 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Democratic National Convention, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  August 10-14
- 96th Congress: General Information, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  November 7
- 99th Congressional Board: Southeastern Clothing Regional Board, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Action- Legislative/ political bulletin of the ACWA, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Steven Mills Workers` Union, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens Workers` Conditions, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: J.P. Stevens (Box 8, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens Second Circuit Case, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- AFL-CLO: Stevens Organizer, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens: Contracts, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  December 16
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Committee, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  April 4
- COPE: TWUA Collections 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- COPE: TWUA Collections, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- COPE: TWUA Collections 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- COPE: TWUA Collections 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Election Contributions: 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- 1975 COPE Contributions (Box 8, Folder 24)
- 1976 COPE Contributions (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Contributions to COPE Funds, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- 1978 Election Result and Analysis (Box 8, Folder 27)
- ACTWU Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- 1982 Mitchell Direct Mail Campaign (Box 9, Folder 1)
- The Impact of Imports on Men`s Clothing Industry, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Direct Mail, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Imports- Leather, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- International Trade Commission-- Gloves, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- TRADE: White Paper on Textile Trade, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  January 5
- TRADE: United States Textile-- The Garment Industry, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- TRADE: Imports to Mexico, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- TRADE: Imports to Columbia, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- TRADE: Imports to Korea, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- TRADE: Imports to Miscellaneous Individual Countries, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- TRADE: Imports to Japan, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- TRADE: Imports to Romania, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- TRADE: Industrial Imports to Canada, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- TRADE: Imports to France, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  December 22
- TRADE: Imports, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- TRADE: Imports- Trade Conference, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- TRADE: Section 807, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- TRADE: Import Statistics, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- TRADE: Import Statistics, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Trade Act of 1974, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- TRADE: Import Statistics, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- TRADE: Industry Licenses, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- TRADE: Import Statistics, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- House Informal Textile Committee, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Mexico Industrialization: Section 806-807, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  October 12
- Repeal of 807- Customs Modernization, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- TRADE: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- TRADE, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- TRADE, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Burke- Harte Trade Bill, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Congressional Responses, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Trade: general, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Bankruptcy Act Amendments, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Bank Holding Company Act, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Bank Holding, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Farah Strike, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  press clips
- Farah Strike, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Economic Opportunities Act, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Congressional District Kit, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- ACWA Congressional District Committees, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- APEC Contributions, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- PAC Checkoff (Voluntary), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- 1979 CDC Program (Box 11, Folder 10)